<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Review on Alex's Blog</title><link>https://burk.blog/categories/review/</link><description>Recent content in Review on Alex's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2020. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 13:19:18 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://burk.blog/categories/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[Initial Impressions] The Shoe Mart: Alden Ravello Indys</title><link>https://burk.blog/posts/alden-ravello-indys-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 13:19:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://burk.blog/posts/alden-ravello-indys-ii/</guid><description>Alden Ravello Indy boots from The Shoe Mart
Background As many know, getting on a list for rare colors of Alden shell can be difficult and once you&amp;rsquo;re on a list there are tales of people waiting upwards of 3-5 years for a chance to buy the shoes they want. I seem to have lucked out a bit. I got on The Shoe Mart&amp;rsquo;s (TSM) list back in December of 2018 and got the email that I was at the front of the line for a model I was interested in in early June of this hellish year.</description></item><item><title>Cavour Co Tassel Loafers Review</title><link>https://burk.blog/posts/cavour-co-tassel-loafers-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 17:04:32 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://burk.blog/posts/cavour-co-tassel-loafers-review/</guid><description>I had been eyeing Cavour&amp;rsquo;s house brand for quite some time. Their shoes are made in Spain Goodyear welt (GYW) construction in lots of solid leathers for around +$320 with a few really nice details that I love. They went on sale for around $250 so I jumped on a pair of brown suede tassel loafers.
Cavour Loafers and goodies
I was drawn to Cavour&amp;rsquo;s house brand partly because of the price-point, but also a lot of the construction details that put these over the top for me.</description></item><item><title>Bedos Leatherworks Toe Taps Review</title><link>https://burk.blog/posts/bedos-toe-taps-review/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burk.blog/posts/bedos-toe-taps-review/</guid><description>Bedo&amp;rsquo;s Leather Works is a cobbler business located in Falls Church VA and is currently run by Steve Doudaklian. Steve does a lot of amazing work on seemingly anything made of leather. You might be familiar with some of his videos where he restored a pair of Allen Edmonds Strands or his famous Florshiem restorations. Check out his YoutTube channel it&amp;rsquo;s mesmerizing.
New Alden Loafers
I recently got a pair of wonderful Alden shell loafers from Brick &amp;amp; Mortar Seattle (above) and I wanted to extend the life of the soles a little.</description></item></channel></rss>