<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GYW on Alex's Blog</title><link>https://burk.blog/categories/gyw/</link><description>Recent content in GYW on Alex's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2020. All rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 20:37:51 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://burk.blog/categories/gyw/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Suede is NOT Delicate</title><link>https://burk.blog/posts/suede-rant/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 20:37:51 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://burk.blog/posts/suede-rant/</guid><description>Myth: suede is delicate.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know how the myth got started, it&amp;rsquo;s entirely false. Real suede is an incredibly durable leather. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t show surface scratches or stains very much. It can get literally soaked and bounce right back. It&amp;rsquo;s incredibly easy to care for; it&amp;rsquo;s receptive to neglect and papering.
Oak Street Bootmakers &amp;#43;7yrs of wear
These blucher mocassins from Oak Street Bootmakers are over 7 years old and they&amp;rsquo;ve been worn quite hard.</description></item><item><title>Collection 2022</title><link>https://burk.blog/posts/collection-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 15:16:27 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://burk.blog/posts/collection-2022/</guid><description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t taken stock of my collection in a little while so since I&amp;rsquo;ve been stuck inside with COVID I took some pictures and decided to write this up about my main rotation.
Alden Ravello Indy boots from The Shoe Mart
The grails of my collection. Alden Indy boots in Ravello shell cordovan from The Shoe Mart. These frankly have the most aggressive sole aside from my hiking boots, so I wear them when it snows.</description></item><item><title>20 Month Review: Alden Unlined Snuff Suede LHS</title><link>https://burk.blog/posts/snuff-lhs-20-month-review/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 16:04:57 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://burk.blog/posts/snuff-lhs-20-month-review/</guid><description>Alden Snuff Suede LHS Loafers from Alden of DC
Background These bad bois are probably my favorite shoes. I was no stranger to snuff suede before this pair (see below), but I always admired this model from afar. In late 2019 I decided to bite the bullet and headed into Alden of DC to see what they had. Helpful as ever I was able to determine my size, but the shade of snuff on the pair they had in-store was a bit too brown for me.</description></item><item><title>Shoe Care Without Being a Nerd</title><link>https://burk.blog/posts/shoe-care-without-being-a-nerd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 21:47:01 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://burk.blog/posts/shoe-care-without-being-a-nerd/</guid><description>Inspired by How to Love Cast Iron Without Being a Nerd About It by Internet Shaquille .
Shoe care can seem really daunting and difficult. You&amp;rsquo;ve heard all about this &amp;ldquo;Goodyear Welt&amp;rdquo; thing and finally sent it and spent more on a pair of shoes than you thought was humanly possible. They&amp;rsquo;re supposed to last, but what do you need to do to get the best life out of them?</description></item><item><title>[Initial Impressions] The Shoe Mart: Alden Ravello Indys</title><link>https://burk.blog/posts/alden-ravello-indys-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 13:19:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://burk.blog/posts/alden-ravello-indys-ii/</guid><description>Alden Ravello Indy boots from The Shoe Mart
Background As many know, getting on a list for rare colors of Alden shell can be difficult and once you&amp;rsquo;re on a list there are tales of people waiting upwards of 3-5 years for a chance to buy the shoes they want. I seem to have lucked out a bit. I got on The Shoe Mart&amp;rsquo;s (TSM) list back in December of 2018 and got the email that I was at the front of the line for a model I was interested in in early June of this hellish year.</description></item></channel></rss>